Guide to the Brooklyn Historical Society ephemera collection ARC.272
Brooklyn Historical Society
Brooklyn Historical Society ephemera collection
1814-2001
Brooklyn Historical Society
ARC.272
19.85 Linear Feet in 9 filing cabinet drawers and 2 oversize flat boxes.
The Brooklyn Historical Society ephemera collection is an artificial collection compiled by Brooklyn Historical Society staff, that continues to be updated to the present day. The collection contains pamphlets, cards, advertisements, newspaper articles, magazines, and more, dating from 1770 to the present documenting Brooklyn, New York City, and Long Island.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to researchers without restriction.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Brooklyn ephemera collection is continually growing and is comprised of a variety of materials donated over the years. Much of its provenance is unknown due to it being a collection of various donations from benefactors both inside and outside Brooklyn Historical Society. Dedication package for the Verrazano-Narrows Bridge is the gift of David E. Simon.
Separated Materials
Ephemera related to the Brooklyn Dodgers baseball club has been removed to form the Brooklyn Dodgers collection (ARC.297).
Scope and Contents
The Brooklyn Historical Society ephemera collection is an artificial collection compiled by Brooklyn Historical Society staff, that continues to be updated to the present day. The collection contains pamphlets, cards, advertisements, newspaper articles, magazines, and more, dating from 1770 to the present documenting Brooklyn, New York City, and Long Island.
Business related materials in this collection include items such as checks, receipts, business and trade cards, bank notes, bank statements of condition, and promotional announcements and brochures. Religious materials include issues of the periodical The Parish News, dating between 1905 and 1906, as well as items pertaining to various Brooklyn churches that existed during the early 19th century, such as the Brooklyn Tabernacle, First Presbyterian Church, Saint Barnabas Church, and Saint Michael's Church of Bay Ridge. Tickets, pamphlets, service programs, announcements, miscellaneous flyers, newspaper clippings, and obituaries can be found here
A variety of materials documents civil organizations, including newsletters, special announcements, and invitations. Invitations to Fire Department balls and galas can be found, some dating to the 1840s. The Parks folder contains materials relating to Prospect Park, ceremonial dedications, annual reports, tour programs, and invitations. Also included are materials related to specific celebrations such as the Hudson-Fulton celebration of 1909, the Williamsburg Bridge opening of 1903, the Long Island Tercentenary Banquet of 1936, the George Washington Centennial celebration of 1889, and the Bicentennial of 1975 to 1977. Brooklyn clubs materials include theater programs, event, menu, and announcement information. Pamphlets, seating lists, donor lists, bulletins, handbooks, and correspondence, all relating to theater programs.
The majority of materials pertaining to entertainment is theater programs, as well as event programs and announcement materials. Theaters are listed alphabetically, and include The Athenaeum, Brooklyn Academy of Music, The Majestic, Montauk Theater, New Brighton Theater, and Payton's Theater, as well as various theaters not documented extensively enough to occupy individual folders, such as the Germania Theater, Brooklyn College Theater, Prospect Hall, and the Carnegie Theater. Each folder contains items such as programs, booklets, and tickets. The collection also includes musical compositions, Coney Island memorabilia, opera programs, and playbills. Materials include event calendars, promotions, programs, annual schedules, newspaper clippings, posters, flyers, brochures, and sales guides. Sports events are documented through miscellaneous tickets and newspaper clippings. It also contains programs and schedules from the Crescent Football Club (1891-1892), the Brooklyn Prep Midgets' football team (1922), the Brooklyn-Queens Marathon and Indoor Games (1926), the Brooklyn Dodgers Football team (1940), and the Brooklyn Cyclones minor league baseball team (2001).
Materials related to the military pertains to the 23rd Regiment, the Navy and the Brooklyn Navy Yard, memorial services, Memorial Day celebrations, Ulysses S. Grant, and miscellaneous notices, a 1918 World War I Christmas postcard, invitations, and announcements. Included are identification cards, like Frances Haber's Brooklyn Navy Yard I.D. dating from 1943. Other items of interest include tickets and invitations for veterans' events and celebrations.
Transportation is represented through identification cards, tickets, booklets and more, pertaining to trains, underground and elevated subways, highways, ferries and bridges.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged alphabetically by subject.
Biographical / Historical
The Brooklyn ephemera collection contains materials of mixed provenance accumulated over decades by the Brooklyn Historical Society(now the Center for Brooklyn History).
Receipts (financial records); Programs (documents); Trade cards (advertising); Admission tickets; Entertainment events |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Clubs -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Railroads |z New York (State) |z Long Island; Railroads |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Clippings (information artifacts); Certificates; Comic books; Correspondence; Magazines (periodicals); Invitations; Pamphlets; Menus; African Americans -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.) |x Religious life and customs; Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.) |x Social life and customs; Brownstone buildings |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Brooklyn Bridge (New York, N.Y.); Prospect Park (New York, N.Y.); Department stores |z New York (State) |z Kings County |x History; Racing |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Theater |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Sports -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Williamsburg Bridge (New York, N.Y.); Popular music |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Music |z New York (State) |z Kings County; United States |x Armed Forces; United States |x History |y Revolution, 1775-1783 |x Centennial celebrations, etc.; Newsletters; Annual reports; Brochures; Calendars; Printed ephemera; Brooklyn Cyclones (Baseball team); Baruch, Bernard M. (Bernard Mannes); Brooklyn Chamber of Commerce (Brooklyn, New York, N.Y.); Brooklyn Public Library; Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation; Brooklyn Academy of Music; Brooklyn Athenaeum
- African-Americans -- Black History (3 folders) (Drawer 2)
- Architecture -- General (2 folders) (Drawer 2)
- Art and Artists -- Authors, undated (Drawer 2)
- Art and Artists -- General (4 folders) (Drawer 2)
- Art and Artists -- Public Art Fund (Drawer 2)
- Art and Artists -- William Sidney Mount, undated (Drawer 2)
- Banks -- General (2 folders), undated (Drawer 2)
- Banks -- Brooklyn Savings Bank, undated (Drawer 2)
- Banks -- Brooklyn Trust Company, undated (Drawer 2)
- Banks -- Dime Savings Bank, undated (Drawer 2)
- Banks -- East NY Savings Bank, undated (Drawer 2)
- Banks -- Hamilton Trust Company, undated (Drawer 2)
- Banks -- South Brooklyn Savings Bank, undated (Box 1)
- Banks -- Williamsburg Savings Bank, undated (Drawer 2)
- Baseball -- Brooklyn Dodgers (2 folders) (Drawer 2)
- Baseball -- Brooklyn Dodgers Predecessors (Drawer 2)
- Brooklyn Bibliography (Drawer 2)
- Bridges -- General (Drawer 2)
- Bridges -- Brooklyn Bridge, circa 1867-1915 (Drawer 2, Box 2, Box 1)
- Bridges -- Brooklyn Bridge, 1920s-1940s (Drawer 2)
- Bridges -- Brooklyn Bridge, 1950s (Drawer 2)
- Bridges -- Brooklyn Bridge, 1970s (Drawer 2)
- Bridges -- Brooklyn Bridge, post-1983 (Drawer 2)
- Bridges -- Brooklyn Bridge -- Centennial, 1983 (Drawer 2)
- Bridges -- Verrazano-Narrows Bridge, undated (Drawer 3)
- Bridges -- Williamsburg Bridge, undated (Drawer 3)
- Buildings -- General, undated (Drawer 3)
- Buildings -- Atlantic Terminal, undated (Drawer 3)
- Buildings -- Barclays Center (Drawer 3)
- Buildings -- Borough Hall (Drawer 3)
- Buildings -- Historic Houses, undated (Drawer 3)
- Buildings -- Lefferts Homestead, undated (Drawer 3)
- Buildings -- Litchfield Villa, undated (Drawer 3)
- Buildings -- MetroTech Center, undated (Drawer 3)
- Buildings -- Old Stone House, undated (Drawer 3)
- Buildings -- Pierrepont Office Building, undated (Drawer 3)
- Buildings -- Williamsburg Savings Bank Building, undated (Drawer 3)
- Buildings -- Wyckoff-Bennett, undated (Drawer 3)
- Buildings -- Wyckoff, Pieter Claesen (Drawer 3)
- Business and Businesses -- General (4 folders) (Drawer 3, Box 1)
- Business and Businesses -- Abraham and Straus (Drawer 3)
- Business and Businesses -- Advertising and Announcements, undated (Drawer 3)
- Business and Businesses -- Breweries, undated (Drawer 3)
- Business and Businesses -- Brooklyn Life Insurance, undated (Drawer 3)
- Business and Businesses -- Business Cards (3 folders), undated (Drawer 3)
- Business and Businesses -- Checks (Drawer 3)
- Business and Businesses -- Elliott Ear Protector, undated (Drawer 3)
- Business and Businesses -- Pfizer, undated (Drawer 3)
- Business and Businesses -- Promotional Advancement and Brochures, undated (Drawer 3)
- Business and Businesses -- Stock Certificates, undated (Drawer 3)
- Business and Businesses -- Stur-dee Health Products (Drawer 3)
- Business and Businesses -- Sugar (2 boxes), undated (Box 3, Box 4)
- Business and Businesses -- Mays Employee Association (2 folders), undated (Drawer 3)
- Calendars, undated (Box 1)
- Cemeteries -- General, undated (Drawer 3)
- Cemeteries -- Cemetery of the Evergreens, undated (Drawer 3)
- Cemeteries -- Cypress Hill Abbey, undated (Drawer 3)
- Cemeteries -- Greenwood Cemetery (2 folders), undated (Drawer 3, Box 2)
- Charities -- Brooklyn Bureau of Community Service (2 folders), undated (Drawer 3)
- Charities -- General, undated (Drawer 3)
- Churches -- General (2 folders) (Drawer 3)
- Churches -- African Methodist Episcopal/Baptist Churches General, undated (Drawer 3)
- Churches -- African Wesleyan Methodist Episcopal Church, undated (Drawer 3)
- Churches -- All Saints' Church, undated (Drawer 3)
- Churches -- Bethany Baptist Church of Brooklyn, undated (Drawer 3)
- Churches -- Brooklyn Tabernacle, undated (Drawer 3)
- Churches -- Church of the Pilgrims, undated (Drawer 3)
- Churches -- Church of the Redeemer, undated (Drawer 3)
- Churches -- Church Promotional Documents and Invitations, undated (Drawer 3)
- Churches -- First Presbyterian Church of Brooklyn, undated (Drawer 3)
- Churches -- First Presbyterian of Brooklyn, undated (Drawer 3)
- Churches -- First Unitarian Church, undated (Drawer 3)
- Churches -- Flatlands Reformed Church, undated (Drawer 3)
- Churches -- Greenpoint Reformed Church, undated (Drawer 3)
- Churches -- Hanson Place Central Methodist Church, undated (Drawer 3)
- Churches -- Lafayette Avenue Presbyterian Church, undated (Drawer 3)
- Churches -- Methodist Episcopal, undated (Drawer 3)
- Churches -- Miscellaneous, undated (Drawer 3)
- Churches -- Parish News, Church of the Holy Trinity, undated (Drawer 3)
- Churches -- Plymouth Church of the Pilgrims, undated (Drawer 3)
- Churches -- Reformed Protestant Dutch Church, undated (Drawer 3)
- Churches -- Roman Catholic, undated (Drawer 3)
- Churches -- Service Programs, undated (Drawer 3)
- Churches -- Spencer Memorial Church, undated (Drawer 4)
- Churches -- St. Ann and the Holy Trinity Episcopal Church, undated (Drawer 4)
- Churches -- St. Barnabas Church, undated (Drawer 4)
- Churches -- St. Francis Xavier Church, undated (Drawer 4)
- Churches -- St. Michael's Roman Catholic Church, Bay Ridge (2 folders) (Drawer 4)
- Churches -- St. Peter and Paul's Church, undated (Drawer 4)
- Churches -- St. Teresa of Avila, undated (Drawer 4)
- Churches -- Sunday school/Anniversary Day Parade, undated (Drawer 4)
- Churches -- Tickets to Church Events, undated (Drawer 4)
- Churches -- Trinity Church, undated (Drawer 4)
- Clubs -- General, undated (Drawer 4)
- Clubs -- American Legion, undated (Drawer 4)
- Clubs -- Apollo Club, undated (Drawer 4)
- Clubs -- Bay Ridge Reading Club, undated (Drawer 4)
- Clubs -- Brooklyn Club, undated (Drawer 4)
- Clubs -- Cambridge Club, undated (Drawer 4)
- Clubs -- City History Club, undated (Drawer 4)
- Clubs -- Crescent Athletic Club, undated (Drawer 4)
- Clubs -- Elks Club, undated (Drawer 4)
- Clubs -- Hamilton Club, undated (Drawer 4)
- Clubs -- Literary Society, undated (Drawer 4)
- Clubs -- Lotus Club, undated (Drawer 4)
- Clubs -- Masons, undated (Drawer 4)
- Clubs -- Miscellaneous Banquet Menus, undated (Drawer 4)
- Clubs -- Miscellaneous Social Clubs (2 folders) (Drawer 4)
- Clubs -- Montauk Club (2 folders) (Drawer 4)
- Clubs -- Musical Societies, undated (Drawer 4)
- Clubs -- Prospect Club, undated (Drawer 4)
- Clubs -- Riding and Driving Club, undated (Drawer 4)
- Clubs -- Union Club, undated (Drawer 4)
- Clubs -- Upanin Haven Club, undated (Drawer 4)
- Clubs -- YMCA/YWCA (Drawer 4, Box 1)
- Community Development (2 folders) (Drawer 4)
- Crime and Law Enforcement, undated (Drawer 4)
- Department Stores (Drawer 4)
  Scope and Contents
  Including Namm's.
- Entertainment -- Bargemusic (Drawer 4)
- Entertainment -- Brooklyn Amateur Musical Club, undated (Drawer 4)
- Entertainment -- Brooklyn Quartet Club, undated (Drawer 4)
- Entertainment -- Classical Soiree Tickets, undated (Drawer 4)
- Entertainment -- Concert Program 1873, undated (Drawer 4)
- Entertainment -- Dance, undated (Drawer 4)
- Entertainment -- German Concert, undated (Drawer 4)
- Entertainment -- Miscellaneous Programs/Announcements of Special Events (2 folders), undated (Drawer 4)
- Entertainment -- Miscellaneous Theater Programs and Announcements (Drawer 4)
- Entertainment -- Musaeola Association, undated (Drawer 4)
- Entertainment -- Musical Compositions, undated (Drawer 4)
- Entertainment -- Musicale in Aid of King's Daughter's Nursery, undated (Drawer 4)
- Entertainment -- Opera Programs, undated (Drawer 4)
- Entertainment -- Program Scrapbooks, undated (Drawer 4)
- Ethnic Groups -- General, undated (Drawer 4)
- Ethnic Groups -- Ethnic Bias, undated (Drawer 4)
- Ethnic Groups -- Chinese, undated (Drawer 4)
- Ethnic Groups -- Dutch, undated (Drawer 4)
- Ethnic Groups -- Finnish-American, undated (Drawer 4)
- Ethnic Groups -- German (Drawer 4)
  Including Turnverein associations.
- Ethnic Groups -- Hispanic, undated (Drawer 4)
- Ethnic Groups -- Immigration, undated (Drawer 4)
- Ethnic Groups -- Irish-American, undated (Drawer 4)
- Ethnic Groups -- Italian, undated (Drawer 4)
- Ethnic Groups -- Japanese, undated (Drawer 4)
- Ethnic Groups -- Jewish, undated (Drawer 4)
- Ethnic Groups -- West Indian (Drawer 4)
- Events -- General (Drawer 4)
- Events -- Bicentennial (2 folders) (Drawer 4)
- Events -- Celebrations Hudson-Fulton, undated (Drawer 4)
- Events -- George Washington Centennial, undated (Drawer 4)
- Events -- Long Island Tercentenary, undated (Drawer 4)
- Events -- Private Social Invitations (Drawer 4)
- Fashion, undated (Drawer 4)
- Film and Television -- General, undated (Drawer 4)
- Film and Television -- The Honeymooners, undated (Drawer 4)
- Firefighting -- General, undated (Drawer 4)
- Firefighting -- Fire Department, undated (Drawer 4)
- Food, Restaurants, Eating -- General (2 folders) (Drawer 5, Box 1)
- Food, Restaurants, Eating -- Gage and Tollner, undated (Drawer 5)
- Food, Restaurants, Eating -- Menus (2 folders), undated (Drawer 5, Box 2)
- Garbage and Waste Management, undated (Drawer 5)
- Genealogy -- Family Histories, undated (Drawer 5)
- Health, Hospitals and Healthcare -- General (2 folders), undated (Drawer 5)
- Health, Hospitals, and Healthcare -- Brooklyn Hospital, undated (Drawer 5)
- Health, Hospitals, and Healthcare -- Flushing Hospital, undated (Drawer 5)
- Health, Hospitals, and Healthcare -- Industrial Home for the Blind, undated (Drawer 5)
- Health, Hospitals, and Healthcare -- Long Island College Hospital (Drawer 5, Box 1)
- Health, Hospitals, and Healthcare -- New York Methodist Hospital, undated (Drawer 5)
- Historic Preservation, undated (Box 1)
- History -- Battle of Long Island (2 folders) (Drawer 5)
- History -- General, undated (Drawer 5)
- Hotels, undated (Drawer 5)
- Hotels -- Hotel St. George, undated (Drawer 5)
- Industries -- General (2 folders) (Drawer 5)
- Industries -- Ship Building, undated (Drawer 5)
- Labor -- Labor Disputes/Strikes, undated (Drawer 5)
- Labor -- Labor Disputes/Strikes -- Boards of Trade, undated (Drawer 5)
- Labor -- Unions, undated (Drawer 5)
- Landmarks Preservation Commission (2 folders) (Drawer 5)
- Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and Transgender (LGBT), undated (Drawer 5)
- Libraries -- General, undated (Drawer 5)
- Libraries -- Brooklyn Public Library (3 folders) (Drawer 5)
- Literature, undated (Drawer 5)
- Mayors, undated (Drawer 5)
- Military, undated (Drawer 5)
- Military -- 23rd Regiment, undated (Drawer 5)
- Military -- Memorial Day Ceremonies, undated (Drawer 5)
- Military -- Memorial Services, undated (Drawer 5)
- Military -- Miscellaneous Notices, Invitations, Announcements, undated (Drawer 5)
- Military -- Regimental Receptions, undated (Drawer 5)
- Military -- Ulysses S. Grant, undated (Drawer 5)
- Monuments and Statues, undated (Drawer 5)
- Museums -- Brooklyn Children's Museum, undated (Drawer 5)
- Museums -- Brooklyn Museum (3 folders) (Drawer 5, Drawer 6)
- Museums -- General, undated (Drawer 6)
- Music (Drawer 6, Box 1)
- Native Americans, undated (Drawer 6)
- Navy Yard (3 folders) (Drawer 6, Box 1)
- Neighborhoods -- General (Drawer 6)
- Neighborhoods -- Bay Ridge, undated (Drawer 6)
- Neighborhoods -- Bedford-Stuyvesant (3 folders) (Drawer 6)
- Neighborhoods -- Bensonhurst, undated (Drawer 6)
- Neighborhoods -- Boerum Hill, undated (Drawer 6)
- Neighborhoods -- Borough Park, undated (Drawer 6)
- Neighborhoods -- Brighton Beach, undated (Drawer 6)
- Neighborhoods -- Brooklyn Heights (4 folders) (Drawer 6, Box 2)
- Neighborhoods -- Brooklyn Heights Promenade, undated (Drawer 6)
- Neighborhoods -- Brownsville, undated (Drawer 6)
- Neighborhoods -- Bushwick, undated (Drawer 6)
- Neighborhoods -- Canarsie, undated (Drawer 6)
- Neighborhoods -- Carroll Gardens, undated (Drawer 6)
- Neighborhoods -- Clinton Hill, undated (Drawer 6)
- Neighborhoods -- Cobble Hill, undated (Drawer 6)
- Neighborhoods -- Coney Island (2 folders) (Drawer 6)
- Neighborhoods -- Crown Heights, undated (Drawer 6)
- Neighborhoods -- Cypress Hills, undated (Drawer 6)
- Neighborhoods -- Ditmas Park, undated (Drawer 6)
- Neighborhoods -- Downtown Brooklyn, undated (Drawer 6)
- Neighborhoods -- DUMBO, undated (Drawer 6)
- Neighborhoods -- Dyker Heights, undated (Drawer 6)
- Neighborhoods -- East New York, undated (Drawer 6)
- Neighborhoods -- Flatbush (2 folders), undated (Drawer 6, Box 1)
- Neighborhoods -- Flatlands, undated (Drawer 6)
- Neighborhoods -- Fort Greene (2 folders), undated (Drawer 6, Box 1)
- Neighborhoods -- Fort Hamilton, undated (Drawer 7)
- Neighborhoods -- Fulton Ferry, undated (Drawer 7)
- Neighborhoods -- Gerritsen Beach Mill, undated (Drawer 7)
- Neighborhoods -- Gowanus, undated (Drawer 7)
- Neighborhoods -- Gravesend, undated (Drawer 7)
- Neighborhoods -- Greenpoint, undated (Drawer 7)
- Neighborhoods -- Kensington, undated (Drawer 7)
- Neighborhoods -- Lefferts Garden, undated (Drawer 7)
- Neighborhoods -- Manhattan Beach, undated (Drawer 7)
- Neighborhoods -- Marine Park, undated (Drawer 7)
- Neighborhoods -- Midwood, undated (Drawer 7)
- Neighborhoods -- Mill Basin, undated (Drawer 7)
- Neighborhoods -- New Lots, undated (Drawer 7)
- Neighborhoods -- Park Slope (3 folders), undated (Drawer 7, Box 1, Box 2)
- Neighborhoods -- Prospect Heights, undated (Drawer 7)
- Neighborhoods -- Prospect Park South, undated (Drawer 7)
- Neighborhoods -- Prospect-Lefferts Gardens, undated (Drawer 7)
- Neighborhoods -- Red Hook, undated (Drawer 7)
- Neighborhoods -- Seagate, undated (Drawer 7)
- Neighborhoods -- Sheepshead Bay, undated (Drawer 7)
- Neighborhoods -- South Brooklyn, undated (Drawer 7)
- Neighborhoods -- Stuyvesant Heights, undated (Drawer 7)
- Neighborhoods -- Sunset Park, undated (Drawer 7)
- Neighborhoods -- Vinegar Hill, undated (Drawer 7)
- Neighborhoods -- Weeksville (2 folders) (Drawer 7)
- Neighborhoods -- Williamsburg (2 folders) (Drawer 7)
- Neighborhoods -- Windsor Terrace, undated (Drawer 7)
- Newspapers (Box 2)
- Newspapers -- The Union, undated (Box 2)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- General, undated (Drawer 8)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- 28th Ward Taxpayers Protective Association, undated (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- 651 Arts (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- American Institute of Architects, undated (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Angel Guardian - Children and Family Services, undated (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- The Arbuckle Institute (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Beca (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corp., undated (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Better Brooklyn Committee, undated (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Borough Park Historical Society, undated (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Boy Scouts, undated (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Boys Welfare Foundation, undated (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn Arts and Culture Association (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn Arts Council (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn Bar Association, undated (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn Benevolent Society, undated (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn Chamber of Commerce, undated (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn Civil Council, undated (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn Economic Development Corporation, undated (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn Heights Association, undated (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn Information and Culture (BRIC) (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn Institutional Council (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn In Touch, undated (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences, undated (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn Red Cross, undated (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn Rotary Club, undated (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brownstone Revival Committee, undated (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- CAMBA, undated (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Center for Holocaust Studies (Drawer 7)
- Organizations and Institutions -- Center for Urban Pedagogy (CUP) (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Civic Orgs General (4 folders) (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Clinton Hill Society, undated (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Community Orgs, Activism, Social Justice (Drawer 7)